Taylor Roberts

Full-Stack Web Developer with a background in critical care nursing. My professional experience has given me critical thinking skills, the ability to work under extreme pressure, and familiarity with working in a team setting. Bootcamp has developed my skills in MERN stack and I'm hopeful for opportunities to continue learning.

Arlington, VA 22209 (239) 628-8939 tstarrroberts@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Children's National Hospital, Washington, DC — *Pediatric Critical Care Registered Nurse*

July 2020 - Present

Preceptor to incoming nurses and bedside nurse in the pediatric intensive care unit at this level 1 trauma center.

Golisano Children's Hospital, Ft. Myers, FL — *Pediatric Critical Care Registered Nurse*

July 2017 - June 2020

Bedside nurse in the pediatric intensive care unit, instructed the pediatric code blue class in the Intern Development Program, and developed a worksheet for pediatric medication dosage calculations.

EDUCATION

George Washington University, Washington, DC — Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development Bootcamp

February 2022 - July 2022

Western Governors University, Virtual Learning — BS Nursing

January 2019 - April 2020

Florida SouthWestern State College, Ft. Myers, FL — AS Nursing

August 2014 - May 2017

PROJECTS

The Grade Gatsby

GitHub: https://github.com/britbolt/grade-gatsby

Deployed app: https://grade-gatsby.herokuapp.com/

Full-stack grade book application created in a group setting that allows teachers to record grades and students to view grades.

HTML | CSS | Bootstrap | JavaScript | jQuery | mySQL | Sequelize

Thought Provoking

GitHub: https://github.com/taystarr/thought-provoking

Independently built back-end social media application tested in Insomnia, allows for new user creation, user to create thoughts, comments, and add friends.

JavaScript | MongoDB | Mongoose | Express

LINKS

GitHub:

https://github.com/taystarr

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/taylor-roberts-a9812aa9/

Online Portfolio:

https://taystarr.github.io/react
-portfolio/

SKILLS

HTML 5

CSS

Bootstrap

JavaScript

Node.js

Express.js

React.js

SQL | Sequelize

MongoDB | Mongoose

GraphQL

PROFESSIONAL AWARDS & ACTIVITIES

Secretary for Quality/Education Council at Golisano Children's Hospital

U.S. Figure Skating Senior Gold Medalist